Guide to the Stanford University, Michelle R. Clayman Institute for Gender Research, Records SC0705
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Records, Accession ARCH-2004-215
  - Corporate Associates
    - Corporate Seminar 5119182--1 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Corporate Seminar 5/19/82--2 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Corporate Seminar 1981 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Seminar for Corporates June 25,1980 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous Corporations (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - ACI, Us, Inc. (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - ADAPTEC (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - ADVANCED MICRO DEVICES (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - ALLSTATE CORPORATION (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - ALZA CORPORATION (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - AMERICAN EXPRESS (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - AMPEX CORPORATION (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - APPLE COMPUTER INC. (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - ASK Systems (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - AVON CORPORATION (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - BANK OF CALIFORNIA (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - BOISIE CASCADE CORPORATION (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - BUSINESS ENTERPRISE TRUST (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - CARNEGIE CORPORATION (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - CAREER ACTION CENTER (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - CHEVRON USA (Box 30, Folder 21)
    - CLOROX (Box 30, Folder 22)
    - COMMONWEALTH CLUB EVENT (Box 30, Folder 23)
    - CONFIDENCE TRAINING INC. (Box 30, Folder 24)
    - CONSULTING PSYCHOLOGISTS PRESS (Box 30, Folder 25)
    - CORNISH AND CAREY RESIDENTIAL (Box 30, Folder 26)
    - THE CORPORATE WORKOUT (Box 30, Folder 27)
    - CROWN ZELLERBACH COMPANY (Box 30, Folder 28)
    - DEL MONTE (Box 30, Folder 29)
    - DIGITAL EQUIPMENT CORPORATION (Box 30, Folder 30)
    - EARLY LEARNING INSTITUTE (Box 30, Folder 31)
    - EQUITEC (Box 30, Folder 32)
    - THE FINANCIAL WOMEN'S ASSOCIATION OF SAN FRANCISCO (Box 30, Folder 33)
    - FORD AREOSPACE (Box 30, Folder 34)
    - FOREMOST-MCKESSON CORPORATION (Box 30, Folder 35)
    - FOX & CARSKADON (Box 30, Folder 36)
    - H.B. FULLER (Box 30, Folder 37)
    - GENENTECH INC. (Box 30, Folder 38)
    - GETTY OIL COMPANY (Box 30, Folder 39)
    - GIARETrO INSTITUTE (Box 30, Folder 40)
    - THE GIANTURCO COMPANY (Box 30, Folder 41)
    - GOLDMAN AND COMPANY (Box 30, Folder 42)
    - HEWLETT PACKARD (Box 30, Folder 43)
    - HYATT RICKEYS (Box 30, Folder 44)
    - IBM (9/88) (Box 30, Folder 45)
    - IBM (9/83-8/88/ (Box 30, Folder 46)
    - IBM (1/76-8/83) (Box 30, Folder 47)
    - INTEL CORPORATION (Box 30, Folder 48)
    - KAISER ALUMINUM (Box 30, Folder 49)
    - KAISER INDUSTRIES CORPORATION (Box 30, Folder 50)
    - KAISER PERMANENTE (Box 30, Folder 51)
    - KINDLING CORPORATION (Box 30, Folder 52)
    - KORN/FERRY INTERNATIONAL (Box 30, Folder 53)
    - KPMG PEAT MARWICK (Box 30, Folder 54)
    - KRAMES COMMUNICATIONS (Box 30, Folder 55)
    - LEVI STRAUSS AND COMPANY (Box 30, Folder 56)
    - Linkage Inc. (Box 30, Folder 57)
    - LITHOTYPE COMPANY (Box 30, Folder 58)
    - LOCKHEED MISSILES AND SPACE (Box 30, Folder 59)
    - MACYS (Box 30, Folder 60)
    - MEASUREX CORPORATION (Box 30, Folder 61)
    - MERVYNS (Box 30, Folder 62)
    - M2 INC. (Box 30, Folder 63)
    - NATIONAL SEMI-CONDUCTOR CORP. (Box 30, Folder 64)
    - NEIMAN MARCUS (Box 30, Folder 65)
    - NORTHERN TRUST OF CALIFORNIA (Box 30, Folder 66)
    - OLDER ADULTS CARE MANAGEMENT (Box 30, Folder 67)
    - PACIFIC GAS AND ELECTRIC COMPANY (Box 30, Folder 68)
    - PACIFIC BELL (9/82-8/89) (Box 30, Folder 69)
    - PACIFIC BELL (3/75-8/82) (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - PALO ALTO CHAMBER OF COMMERCE (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - PLANTRONICS INCORPORATED (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - THE PORTER GROUP (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - POTLACH CORPORATION (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - RAYCHEM (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - REACH FITNESS (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - ROLM CORPORATION (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - RUSHER, LOSCAVIO, & LOPRESTO (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - SRI INTERNATIONAL (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - SAFEWAY (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - SAGA CORPORATION (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - SEARS ROEBUCK FOUNDATION (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - SILICON GRAPHICS (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - SHAKLEE CORP. (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - SPACE SYSTEMSILORAL (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - STANDARD OIL COMPANY OF CA. (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - STEELCASE INC. (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - SUN MICROSYSTEMS (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - SYNTEX CORPORATION (Box 31, Folder 20)
    - TANDEM CORPORATION (Box 31, Folder 21)
    - TRANSAMERICA CORPORATION (Box 31, Folder 22)
    - TRANS-PACIFIC EXCHANGE (Box 31, Folder 23)
    - TRW AVIONICS (Box 31, Folder 24)
    - 20% BY 2020 (Box 31, Folder 25)
    - UNITED AIRLINES (Box 31, Folder 26)
    - UNITED CALIFORNIA BANK (Box 31, Folder 27)
    - WASTE MANAGEMENT (Box 31, Folder 28)
    - WELLS FARGO CORPORATION (Box 31, Folder 29)
    - WINDHAM HILL PRODUCTIONS INC. (Box 31, Folder 30)
    - WOODSIDE WOMENS HOSPITAL (Box 31, Folder 31)
    - WILMA H. WOOL (Box 31, Folder 32)
- Records, Accession ARCH-2005-079
  - SEI 1995 Course Handouts (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 1995 SEI attendee--August, Judy Jaeger, 1995 Aug. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 1995 SEI attendee--August, Karen Jared, 1995 Aug. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 1995 SEI attendee--August, Sharon Javery, 1995 Aug. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 1995 SEI attendee--August, Constance Johnson, 1995 Aug. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 1995 SEI attendee--August, Pamela Kandziora, 1995 Aug. (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 1995 SEI- August, Dato Fawziah ABd Karim, 1995 Aug. (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 1995 SEI attendee--August, Mary A. Lowden, 1995 Aug. (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 1995 SEI--August, M. Joan McErlean, 1995 Aug. (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - 1995 SEI attendee--August, Brenda Nasser, 1995 Aug. (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - 1995 SEI attendee--August, Karen Perry, 1995 Aug. (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - 1995 SEI attendee--August, Jackie Robinson, 1995 Aug. (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - 1995 SEI attendee--August, Carolyn Rose, 1995 Aug. (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - 1995 SEI attendee--August, Debi Reissman, 1995 Aug. (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - 1995 SEI attendee--August, Linda Russell, 1995 Aug. (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - 1995 SEI attendee--August, Tamar Sherer, 1995 Aug. (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - 1995 SEI attendee--August, Darlene Yaplee, 1995 Aug. (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - 1995 SEI attendee--August, Kimberly Yeager, 1995 Aug. (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - 1995 SEI Applications, August session, 1995 Aug. (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - 1995 SEI attendee--June, Catherine Albertoni, 1995 Jun. (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - 1995 SEI attendee--August, Karen Arnett, 1995 Aug. (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - 1995 SEI attendee--August, Brooke D. Barrett, 1995 Aug. (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - 1995 SEI attendee--August, Susan Boyle, 1995 Aug. (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - 1995 SEI attendee--August, Michel Bitritto, 1995 Aug. (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - 1995 SEI attendee--August, Silvia LaRue Branchcomb, 1995 Aug. (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - 1995 SEI attendee--August, Joan Burke, 1995 Aug. (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - 1995 SEI attendee--August, Linda K. Dannels, 1995 Aug. (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - 1995 SEI attendee--August, Theresa Dobilas, 1995 Aug. (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - 1995 SEI attendee--August, Leslie Eubank, 1995 Aug. (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - 1995 SEI attendee--August, Mary S. Evans, 1995 Aug. (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - 1995 SEI attendee--August, Ovita T. Franz, 1995 Aug. (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - 1995 SEI attendee--July, Gail Garland, 1995 Jul. (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - 1995 SEI attendee--August, Linda Gordon, 1995 Aug. (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - 1995 SEI attendee--August, Sherry Hirsch, 1995 Aug. (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - 1995 SEI attendee--August, Karen Hodge, 1995 Aug. (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - 1995 SEI attendee--August, Colleen M. Hummer, 1995 Aug. (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - 1995 SEI Daily Handouts: Day Three, Myers-Briggs Pumpkin Soup recipe (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - 1995 SEI Daily Handouts: Day Three, Images of Leadership (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - 1995 SEI Daily Handouts: Day Three, Leadership & Management Effectiveness (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - 1995 SEI Daily Handouts: Day Three, Leadership Orientations Dimensions (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - 1995 SEI Daily Handouts: Day One, Mother Wove the Morning information (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - 1995 SEI Daily Handouts: Day One, Informal DInner Reading Discussions (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - 1995 SEI Daily Handouts: Day One, Speaker Leadership Strategies Comp. (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - 1995 SEI--June Session, Pajara Dunes brochures & maps, 1995 Jun. (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - 1995 SEI--June, computer needs, 1995 Jun. (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - 1995 SEI Catering--June catering, 1995 Jun. (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - SEI 1995--Course Plan (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Evaluations--June (SEI), 1995 Jun. (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - SEI 1995--June Participants (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - 1995 SEI Housing--June session, 1995 Jun. (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - 1995 SEI attendee--June, Carol Armitage, 1995 Jun. (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - 1995 SEI attendee--June, Lela Brissett, 1995 Jun. (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - 1995 SEI attendee--June, Diane M. Capstaff, 1995 Jun. (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - 1995 SEI attendee--June, Paula Carter, 1995 Jun. (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - 1995 SEI attendee--June, Vernelle P. DeWitty, 1995 Jun. (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - 1995 SEI attendee--June, Vonnie Estes, 1995 Jun. (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - 1995 SEI attendee--June, Martha Grey, 1995 Jun. (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - 1995 SEI--Press Packet (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - 1995 SEI Press Release (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Business Process Reengineering, Kellog School-Northwestern U., 1992-1994 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - 1995 SEI--Other programs, Competitive pricing & formats (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - 1995 SEI--Other programs, Foundation for Women's Resource (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - 1995 SEI--Other programs, Health Area (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Stanford Leadership Advancement Syposium, 1994-11-18 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Public Health Leadership Inst. CDC & Univ. of CA, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - 1995 SEI--Other Programs, San Jose State (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - 1995 SEI off-site venues (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Pajaro Dunes, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Valley Lodge, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Quail Lodge, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Los Laureles--Carmel Valley, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Alpine Chalet, undated (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Holiday Inn-Stanford, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Meadowood Resort, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - 1995 SEI Speakers, General Information (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - 1995 SEI Speakers--General (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - 1995 SEI Speaker, John Dotson (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Aileen Hernandez, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - 1995 SEI Speaker, Susan M. Lark, M. D. (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Jing Lyman, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Amy McCombs, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Anne Robinson--Windham Hill, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - 1995 SEI speaker, Michaela Rodeno (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - 1995 SEI Speaker, Ronni Sonnenberg (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Luisah Teish, Ph.D., 1995 (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - 1995 SEI Speaker, Tara Van Deveer (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - Stanford Sierra Camp, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - Stone Pine--Carmel Valley, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - Torrey Pines, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - 1995 SEI Mailing List, General Information (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - 1995 SEI--Dun & Bradstreet, Mailing List (Box 1, Folder 91)
  - 1995 SEI mailing list, Forbes (Box 1, Folder 92)
  - 1995 SEI--Mailings, Fortune mailing (Box 1, Folder 93)
  - 1995 SEI mailing list, Phone calls & Fax resp. (Box 1, Folder 94)
  - 1995 SEI mailing list, Paola Gianturco's list (Box 1, Folder 95)
  - 1995 SEI mailing lists, Int. Assoc. Business Comm. (Box 1, Folder 96)
  - 1995 SEI mailing lists, Labels for NY area Women (Box 1, Folder 97)
  - 1995 SEI Media Mailing list (Box 1, Folder 98)
  - 1995 SEI mailing list, Professional Business Wom. (Box 1, Folder 99)
  - 1995 SEI mailing list, Peggy Umanzio's list (Box 1, Folder 100)
  - 1995 SEI Attendee--June session, Karen Johnson, 1995 Jun. (Box 1, Folder 101)
  - 1995 SEI attendee--June, Lloyce Jaunkalnietis, 1995 Jun. (Box 1, Folder 102)
  - 1995 SEI attendee--June, Marianne Littau, 1995 Jun. (Box 1, Folder 103)
  - 1995 SEI attendee--June, Rose H. Malle-Gianattassio, 1995 Jun. (Box 1, Folder 104)
  - 1995 SEI--June, Cheryl M. McFate, 1995 Jun. (Box 1, Folder 105)
  - 1995 SEI Attendee--June session, Karen J. Mulvahill, 1995 Jun. (Box 1, Folder 106)
  - 1995 SEI Attendee--June, Jan Cyre, 1995 Jun. (Box 1, Folder 107)
  - 1995 SEI Attendee--June session, Jacqueline P. McCaffrey, 1995 Jun. (Box 1, Folder 108)
  - 1995 SEI Attendee--June, M.J. Marlinski, 1995 Jun. (Box 1, Folder 109)
  - 1995 SEI Catering--July session, 1995 Jul. (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - 1995 SEI--July computer needs, 1995 Jul. (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - SEI 1995--July Course Plan (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - SEI 1995--July Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - SEI 1995--July Evaluation Forms (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - 1995 SEI--Logistics July, Hartlet Confrence Ctr., 1995 Jul. (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - 1995 SEI Housing--July session, 1995 Jul. (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - 1995 SEI attendee--July, Christine Albertini, 1995 Jul. (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - 1995 SEI attendee--July, Sherie Berger, 1995 Jul. (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - 1995 SEI attendee--July session, Ann L. Brand, 1995 Jul. (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - 1995 SEI attendee--July, Joyce Bromberg, 1995 Jul. (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - 1995 SEI attendee--July, Jennifer Byers, 1995 Jul. (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - 1995 SEI attendee--July session, Sherida I. David, 1995 Jul. (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - 1995 SEI attendee--July session, Kathleen M. Dole, 1995 Jul. (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - 1995 SEI attendee--July, Peggy L. Djurdjulov, 1995 Jul. (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - 1995 SEI attendee--July, Ellen Fleming, 1995 Jul. (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - 1995 SEI attendee--July session, Roxanna Flint, 1995 Jul. (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - 1995 SEI attendee--July, Marilyn Guerrieri, 1995 Jul. (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - 1995 SEI attendee--July, Diane Hulce, 1995 Jul. (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - 1995 SEI attendee--July, Kathy Knutsen, 1995 Jul. (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - 1995 SEI attendee--July, Marion Nierentz, 1995 Jul. (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - 1995 SEI attendee--July session, Lauretta Prestera, 1995 Jul. (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - 1995 SEI attendee--July, Ellen Preston, 1995 Jul. (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - 1995 SEI attendee--July, Rose Rappaport, 1995 Jul. (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - 1995 SEI attendee--July session, Nancy J. Rhine, 1995 Jul. (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - 1995 SEI attendee--July session, Michaelene C. Risley, 1995 Jul. (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - 1995 SEI attendee--July, Carmen Roberts, 1995 Jul. (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - 1995 SEI attendee--July, Linda Roberts, 1995 Jul. (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - 1995 SEI attendee--July, Ramona Shelton-Finch, 1995 Jul. (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - 1995 SEI attendee--July, Lorraine Vance, 1995 Jul. (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - 1995 SEI attendee--July, Susan West, 1995 Jul. (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - 1995 SEI attendee--July, Elease E. Wright, 1995 Jul. (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - ESI: Reception, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - ESI: Wine Reception, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - ESI: Women & Leadership, Sherri's Lecture, undated (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - 1994 SEI Presentation Info (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - ESI: Student Evaluations, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - ESI: Paola and Peggy's Student Follow-up Letter, undated (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - 1994 SEI Wrap-Up (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - ESI: Women and Leadership, Thank You Letters, 1994 Jul. (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - ESI: Women and Leadership, Mailing Lists, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - ESI: Women and Leadership, Mailing Lists (2), 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - ESI: Women and Leadership, Sent Brochures to, undated (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Inquiries--NYT and others, 1994-04-26 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Corporate Lists, undated (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - 1994 ESI Media Mailing List (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Notebook Materials, undated (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - ESI: Women and Leadership, Other Programs, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - ESI: Leadership Orientation, undated (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - ESI: Riso Enneagram, undated (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - ESI: Umanzio/Gianturco Letter, 1994-05-25 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - ESI: Women and Leadership, Housing and Board, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - ESI: Women and Leadership, Invoices and Payments Received, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - ESI: Women and Leadership, Hartley Conference Center, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - ESI: Women and Leadership, Luncheon Speakers, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - ESI: Women and Leadership, Speaker--Anna Eshoo, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - ESI: Women and Leadership, Speaker--Aileen Hernandez, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - ESI: Women and Leadership, Speaker--Jing Lyman, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - ESI: Women and Leadership, Speaker--Anne Robinson, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - ESI: Women and Leadership, Speaker--Luisah Teish, Ph.D., 1994 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Summer Executive Institute, The New York Times article, 1995 Mar. (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - 1995 SEI ads (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - 1995 SEI ad--4" x 2 1/16" lino (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - 1995 SEI--1 5/8" ad lino (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - 1995 SEI Budget (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - 1995 SEI--Expenditures (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Summer Executive Institute, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Summer Executive Institute, General Administration, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - 1995 SEI--Corrine's Business Cards (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - 1995 SEI Administrative Contract w/ Gianturco & Umanzio (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - 1995 SEI Administrative, Corrine Perri contract (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - 1995 SEI Premiums, Totebags (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - 1995 SEI--Scholarship Apps. (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - 1995 SEI Brochure (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - SEI 1995--Leadership Orientation (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - SEI 1995--August Logistics (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - SEI 1995--Myers Briggs Type Indicator (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - SEI 1995--Schedule 8/17-8/25, 1995 Aug. (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - SEI 1995--August Wine Reception (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - SEI 1995--August Computer Needs (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - 1995 SEI--Logistics August, Hartley Conference Ctr., 1995 Aug. (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - SEI 1995--August SU Catering (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - 1995 SEI Housing--August session, 1995 Aug. (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - SEI 1995--August Evaluation Forms (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - ESI: Women and Leadership, Ads and Publicity, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - 1994 SEI Press Release (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - St. Supery Winery, 1996 Feb. (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - ESI: Women and Leadership- "Boss Letters", 1994 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - ESI: Women and Leadership, Brochure Draft, undated (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - ESI: Laman, Denise L., 1994 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - ESI: Matteo, Sherri, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - ESI: Poupon, Roberta, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - ESI: Richardson, Faye, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - ESI: Shuttleworth, Natalie O., 1994 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - ESI: Van Laningham, Evelyn B., 1994 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - ESI: Ward, Caroyln J., 1994 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - ESI: Evanoff, Carol Y., 1994 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - ESI: Finch, Bonnie L., 1994 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - ESI: Flynn, Elizabeth E., 1994 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - ESI: Friel, Janet G., 1994 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - ESI: Garrett-Valentine, Gretchen, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - ESI: Gilligan, (Mary) Karen, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - ESI: Hart, Betty T., 1994 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - ESI: Harvey, Teri L., 1994 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - ESI: Helft, Juliet Z., 1994 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - ESI: Hiatt, Cynthia A., 1994 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - ESI: Hmelar, Anni, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - ESI: Huser, Joan, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - ESI: Aaron, Debra, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - ESI: Ammann, Cathie L., 1994 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - ESI: Berthold, Roberta A., 1994 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - ESI: Billig, Tina L., 1994 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - ESI: Bock, Annie B., 1994 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - ESI: Burds, Judy L., 1994 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - ESI: Busch,-05-C., 1994 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - ESI: Cox, Joan M., 1994 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Summer Institute on Women and Leadership (costs), undated (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - ESI: Cancellations, Applicants, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - ESI: Bell, Susan G., 1994 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - ESI: Haffner, Lynn C., 1994 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - ESI: Palat, Deborah M., 1994 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - ESI: Women and Leadership, Applications Received, undated (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - ESI: Women and Leadership, Brochure--Final, undated (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - ESI 1994 Expenses (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - ESI: CEU, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - ESI: Women and Leadership, Address List of Callers, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - ESI: Sherri's Letter, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - ESI: Women and Leadership Correspondence, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - ESI: Women and Leadership, Course Syllabus, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - ESI: Events and Services Equipment, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Stanford Folder Information, undated (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Human Resources People, 1994 Aug. (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - ESI: Myers-Brigg, undated (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Correspondences/ Memorandums 1995 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - 1995 SEI Correspondence (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - 1995 SEI Course Reader (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - 1995 SEI Course Material, binder inserts--Gianturco C. V. (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - 1995 SEI Course Material, binder inserts--Umanzio C. V. (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - 1995 SEI Course Material Assignments (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - 1995 SEI Course Material, June Binder inserts, 1995 Jun. (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - 1995 SEI Course Materials, Originals for Binders 7/95 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - June Quizzes, 1995 Jun. (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - 1995 SEI Daily Course Handouts (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - 1995 SEI Advertising, California Press Bureau Info. (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - 1995 SEI Advertising, New York Observer (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - 1995 SEI ad, San Francisco Newspaper Agency (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - 1995 SEI Advertising, The Worldpaper (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - 1995 SEI brochure development (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - 1995 SEI brochure--pictures (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - 1995 SEI Brochure, online brochure (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - 1995 SEI--correspondance with Paola Gianturco (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - 1995 SEI--Nikki's updates (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - 1995 SEI Pre-Course Correspon. (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - 1995 SEI--Correspondance withi Peggy Umanzio (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - 1995 SEI Correspondance, SM's letter re: logistics (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - 1995 SEI Pre-Course Correspondance, Shadowing Assignment (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - 1995 SEI--Correspondance, June, 1995 Jun. (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - 1995 SEI--August Correspondance, 1995 Aug. (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Corrine Perri Corresp., 1995 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - 1995 SEI--Continuing Education Credits (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - 1995 SEI Daily Handouts: Day Four, How desirable is it for a man to... (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - 1994 SEI Daily Handouts: Day Four, How desirable is it for a man to... (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - 1995 SEI Daily Handouts: Day Four, Rene Redwood Form (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - 1995 SEI Daily Handouts: Day Four, Catalyst recommendations for policy (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - 1995 SEI Daily Handouts: Day Three, Leadership Orientation Scores (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - 1995 SEI--International (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Enneagram/ Newsweek, etc., 1994 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - 1995 SEI Instruments, Leadership Orientation (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Conference: "Women, Law, & Public Policy", 1987-08-28-30 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - League of Women Voters--March 1996 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Marilyn Yalom--conference, "The Written Life", 1993 Mar. (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Pacfic/ West Coast Project (M. Yalom), 1987-1989 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence re- Conferences, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Japan-U.S. Conference on Women and Family, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Yokohama Forum, General Correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Stanford Daily April 15, 1993, 1993-04-15 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Yokohama Women's Forum, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Sherri Matteo/ Yokohama correspondence 1992 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Yokohama Women's Forum Project: Account Information, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Yokohama Women's Forum Project: Test Results, undated (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Sarah Erickson 1993 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Questionnaires/ References, undated (Box 4, Folder 43)